# DARE SODIQ

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

### INFO

#### **PHONE**

+2348149583661

#### **EMAIL**

daresodiq000@gmail.com

#### **SKILLS**

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

Node JS

React JS

Mongo DB

**REST API** 

GraphQL

TypeScript

# **PROFILE**

A Full Stack Developer with 2 years of experience in Javascript, PHP. Knowledgeable in user interface, testing, and debugging processes. Possessing a love for flexible and agile working environment. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.

## **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

# Backend Engineer, ObigTech

Lagos

Jan 2019 — Present

- Planned, developed, tested, deployed, and maintained web applications.
- · Worked well independently and within a team setting.
- Effectively translated client requirements into application designs and systems requirements.
- Worked as a productive and positive team member to design, code, test, report, and debug operations.

# Junior Web Developer, Tutors Learners Wordwide

Lagos

Aug 2019 — May 2020

- Researched new technologies, software packages and hardware products for use in website projects
- .Completed full redesigns of existing websites to design a friendly User interface also while improving the User experience.
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$  Development of websites with Node js and typescript
- Used programming capabilities in PHP, SQL and JavaScript and other libraries as needed.
- · Worked on eCommerce maintenance and management for client websites.

# **EDUCATION**

# National Diploma, Yaba College of Technology

Lagos

Jan 2015 — Dec 2016

# Higher National Diploma, Yaba College of Technology

Lagos

Aug 2018 — Dec 2019

# INTERNSHIPS

# Web Development, CodeLagos

Lagos

Jan 2015 — Jun 2015

## FRAMEWORKS

Node JS, Express JS, React JS, Nest JS, Flask, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Graphql